Siva Cherukuri

Senior L1 Engineer at Etisalat

sivachows@outlook.com

Summary

I am a Lead Software Engineer with more than 6 years of experience. I have been working in very different markets, that go from Telecom, Banking, Health Care, and IOT.

Besides working with big players, I also spend some of my free time engaging with Open Source projects. You can see some of what I do here:

- https://github.com/sivachows/

I also like to help other people getting better on what they love:

- https://stackoverflow.com/users/3128757/sivacherukuri

Interests:

- Blockchain, Flutter.io

Specialities:

- iOS, Swift, Objective-C, Android, Java, Go lang, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Experience

Senior L1 Engineer at Etisalat June 2018 - Present

Full Stack Mobile Application Developer at Plivo

April 2017 - June 2018 (1 year 3 months)

iOS Developer at Ducere Technologies Pvt Ltd

February 2015 - March 2017 (2 years 2 months)

System Engineer at Tata Consultancy Services

March 2012 - June 2014 (2 years 4 months)

Education

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University, Kakinada

Siva Cherukuri

Senior L1 Engineer at Etisalat

sivachows@outlook.com



Contact Siva on LinkedIn